<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vacation Planner</string>
    <string name="taj_mahal_desc">The Taj Mahal was commissioned by Shah Jahan in 1631, to be built in the memory of his wife Mumtaz Mahal, who died on 17 June that year, while giving birth to their 14th child, Gauhara Begum.Construction started in 1632, and the mausoleum was completed in 1648, while the surrounding buildings and garden were finished five years later. The imperial court documenting Shah Jahan\'s grief after the death of Mumtaz Mahal illustrates the love story held as the inspiration for the Taj Mahal.</string>
    <string name="red_fort_desc">The Red Fort, the largest monument in Delhi, is one of its most popular tourist destinations and attracts thousands of visitors every year. It is a monument of national significance; every year on India\'s Independence Day (15 August), the Prime Minister of India hoists the country\'s flag at the Red Fort and delivers a nationally broadcast speech from its ramparts. The fort also appears on the back of the ₹500 note of the Mahatma Gandhi New Series of the Indian rupee.</string>
    <string name="golden_temple_desc">The Golden Temple (also known as the Harmandir Sahib,or the Darbar Sahib is a gurdwara located in the city of Amritsar, Punjab, India. It is the preeminent spiritual site of Sikhism.</string>
    <string name="cn_tower_desc">The CN Tower (French: Tour CN) is a 553.3 m-high (1,815.3 ft) concrete communications and observation tower located in the downtown core of Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Built on the former Railway Lands, it was completed in 1976. Its name \"CN\" originally referred to Canadian National, the railway company that built the tower. Following the railway\'s decision to divest non-core freight railway assets prior to the company\'s privatization in 1995, it transferred the tower to the Canada Lands Company, a federal Crown corporation responsible for real estate development.</string>
    <string name="niagra_falls_desc">Niagara Falls is a group of three waterfalls at the southern end of Niagara Gorge, spanning the border between the province of Ontario in Canada and the state of New York in the United States. The largest of the three is Horseshoe Falls, also known as Canadian Falls, which straddles the international border of the two countries. The smaller American Falls and Bridal Veil Falls lie within the United States. Bridal Veil Falls is separated from Horseshoe Falls by Goat Island and from American Falls by Luna Island, with both islands situated in New York.</string>
    <string name="mount_rushmore_desc">O say can you see this American wonder? Mount Rushmore is a historic and famous sight that earns its place on any bucket list of the United States. Nestled in South Dakota, this is one of the great, wide-open space attractions that you can spend the day at The main feature of the Mount Rushmore National Memorial is, of course, the four historical figures carved into the mountain. These four are George Washington, Thomas Jefferson, Abraham Lincoln, and Theodore Roosevelt. It is a wonderful mixture of natural, historical, and man-made beauty all in one place.</string>
    <string name="statue_liberty_desc">The Statue of Liberty is one of the most iconic and recognizable landmarks in the whole country. Lady Liberty stands tall over Ellis Island, and all that surrounds (or tours) it. There are several options available for boat tours, photo ops, and so much more to commemorate such a moment. There is little else that could so capture the American spirit in one sight, and the Statue of Liberty is often cited as the place to go. “Give me your tired, your poor, your huddled masses yearning to breathe free”!</string>
    <string name="times_square_desc">Honestly, this could be a city in itself! Times Square is the lively, eccentric, exciting, fast-paced heart of New York City. It is one of the most famous places in the US where street performers come to play, shops open their doors wide, traffic rages on, the billboards are bright, and people from all over the world come together. Times Square is one of a kind New York experience that simply can’t be missed.</string>
    <string name="white_house_desc">The White House in D.C. is the official residence of the President of the United States. This came into tradition with President John Adams in 1800. Since then, it has been a long-honored tradition that the White House be the primary residence of the President, and typically, the President’s family.It is a massive, beautiful, historical building with a gorgeous front lawn and plenty of photo opportunities. There are even free tours available to the public, although there are a few rules and people you will have to contact first. Regardless of the entrance, if you want to see one of the most famous buildings in the United States, the White House should be on that bucket list.</string>
</resources>